OUR STICKY LOVE
After everything today,
you must be tired. When we get home,
wash up and get some sleep.
Yeah, I'll get some sleep, but…
Speaking of sleep…
When will we start sharing a room again?
What?
I believe that you're my boyfriend now.
I have no choice but to,
and I think I've figured out
why I fell for you.
I know you're being considerate
because I lost my memory,
but what if my memory never returns?
Will we sleep in separate rooms forever?
Like we're just housemates?
I'm saying we should start
getting back to normal.
Our plans to get married,
and that we were in love…
I believe it all.
I guess I'm trying to say…
I'd be open to sharing a room
now that I trust you.
Do I need to keep going?
The thing is…
I don't think… we can do that right now.
Why not?
A pleasure to meet you, ma'am!
I'm Kim Gang-rok, Tae-ha's junior.
He came here to settle down
but hasn't found a place yet.
And as you can see, his foot's hurt.
So he's staying here with us
until he finds a place?
Yes, I'll only be here for a little while.
Just think of me as your little brother.
I'm at your disposal, whatever you need.
Yeah, and he'll be sharing my room,
so you don't have to worry about a thing.
Yes, I'll be… What?
-What?
Wouldn't it be better
if you two shared a room
and I slept in a different room?
I think so too.
Still, you're a guest.
It'd be impolite to make you sleep alone.
Since when is that impolite?
Maybe he'll carry you on his back
and sing you a lullaby too.
I don't want to rush into
sharing a room either,
so let's do that, then.
You should sleep with him.
Politely.
Okay, thanks.
"Thanks"?
Have a good night's…
Sir!
What? What is it?
Who does he think he is?
Some kind of saint? Confucian scholar?
Why is he so big on politeness,
making sure his guest sleeps well?
So annoying.
Why did I have to bring up sharing a room?
This is so humiliating.
What the heck is wrong with him?
I mean…
I thought you were
supposed to be her boyfriend.
Shouldn't you share a room
with Prosecutor Go to really sell it?
Just lay out the bedding.
I don't understand you. Not one bit.
Putting the act aside,
you like Prosecutor Go, right?
Then, of course,
you should share a room with her.
Why insist on…
Hold up.
Are you shy?
How cute.
I know you're hopeless
when it comes to women,
but I didn't know
you were such a teenager.
Are you not mentally prepared
to share a room just yet?
Is your heart pounding
because she's your first love?
How exactly do you feel?
Are your nerves getting to you?
I wouldn't know. God, this is killing me.
Seriously, I wouldn't know.
Oh, my stomach.
Do you want to be shaking with fear?
All over?
I'm sorry.
Well,
good night.
But, sir.
Now that she's back,
what are you going to do?
I heard you'll be smuggling her
out of the country.
How do you know that?
When you were busy looking for her,
I asked Mr. Hong.
I knew you wouldn't have saved her
without a plan.
The boat leaves late this month.
Late this month?
I'll send her off then.
If her memory returns by then,
I'm sure she'll leave willingly
to avoid Chairman Baek.
But what if it doesn't?
Then I'll have to force her
to leave the country.
That's the only way she'll be safe.
And let's not call her Prosecutor Go
in this house, even if it's just us.
If she finds out before she remembers,
she'll be at risk.
Yes, understood.
Good night.
Please go on and get some sleep.
I'll be back after a quick smoke.
Okay.
I'll turn off the lights.
Come have breakfast!
You cooked all this by yourself?
I didn't know what you'd like,
so I prepared a variety of cuisines,
from Asia to the Middle East
and even the US.
You won't have to worry about meals
while I'm here.
-Let's eat.
-Okay.
Enjoy your meal!
Looks good.
Of course.
I knew you'd go for that first.
I made this for him all the time
when he was hungover.
His gochujang stew is great.
You should try it.
I don't really like gochujang.
-I'll have this.
-Sure.
Whatever you eat,
just eat a lot and get better.
-And I hope your clinic visit goes well.
-Clinic visit?
Don't you get treatment
on Tuesdays and Fridays?
Did Mr. Hong tell you that too?
I've been your right-hand man
for ten years now.
Keeping tabs on your schedule is a given.
Eat up, and good luck
with your treatment today.
If I remember correctly,
the last time you two were here,
you had a big argument and then left.
I take it things have changed
quite a bit since then?
I haven't regained my memory,
but I guess you could say
I regained my trust in him.
Trust? I see.
Isn't that just how things go
between a man and a woman?
Let's go ahead with the treatment
as planned.
You mentioned physical therapy,
didn't you?
Yes, I did.
It's called TMS, and we use
magnetic pulses on the cerebral cortex,
which stores long-term memory.
If we're lucky,
it will stimulate the area,
and her memory will come back.
Is it painful, by any chance?
Might it cause severe headaches or--
Remember when our teacher whacked you
for picking A's in the multiple choice?
It'll hurt less than that.
So, TMS first, then…
TMS TREATMENT ROOM
You were a mess, saying you were scared
and couldn't believe him and whatnot.
Women sure are hard to read.
Well, things happened.
I believe everything Jang Tae-ha says now.
Then why bother with
getting your memory back?
Because I want to remember our past.
I think it's true
that my life was nothing special,
but Jang Tae-ha
seems to have liked me a lot regardless.
Right now, only he remembers that.
How lonely must that be?
Not being able to share the memories
you made with the person you love.
-Was it okay?
-Yeah, I didn't feel a thing.
Here.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
We'll get going.
Let's go.
Ms. Lee Chae-yeon.
Yes.
That woman who was your classmate.
I have a bad feeling about her.
Why?
Women can easily sniff out other women
who are interested in their men.
The way she defended you
and had a go at me last time.
And the way she looks at you.
Why are you laughing?
Could it be that she likes you?
-No way.
-What do you mean "no way"?
Didn't you see her earlier?
She was doing all this.
Her hair was already tucked
behind her ear.
There was no hair left to tuck,
but she kept doing this.
That's a subconscious way of flirting
to show off her femininity and neckline.
Let's go to the gym.
Mr. Hong's treating us to shrimp.
-Is the treatment she got today effective?
-Thank you.
They can't guarantee anything.
We can only hope for the best.
Sure.
That shrimp's gonna freeze.
-Eat up.
-Okay.
You're really living up to your reputation
as the village romantic.
As if you're the only lovebirds.
We're lovebirds too.
-Here.
-Open up.
Is this a village of love?
I have shrimp whiskers
stuck under my nails
from peeling and eating shrimp
all by my lonesome self.
Here, eat up.
Thank you.
Thanks.
-Hilarious.
-Thanks.
Please go on and get some sleep.
I'll be back after a quick smoke.
So funny.
Thank you.
Is today the day the car will be ready?
Sorry? Yes, it'll be ready today.
He says he bought a good one
to drive you around in.
Shall we pick it up together?
No, thanks.
You're doing all that for me,
so I want to earn my keep.
Earn your keep?
You said I worked
at your grandma's taffy shop.
I should go back to my old job.
I bet I could learn the ropes
pretty quickly.
It didn't look too difficult.
You want me to do all this?
All you have to do is scoop and pour.
What's so hard about that?
Try it.
Do you have any thick gloves I could …
-Grab it already.
-Yes, ma'am.
Such a neat freak.
It's hot!
-Did you burn yourself?
-No, I'm okay.
What should I do?
Oh no.
I'm sorry. Do you have another one?
Do you have a ladle or something?
The taffy would stick to something
like that.
You need to use a lacquered bowl
so the taffy can slide right off!
So there's a reason for everything.
I'm so sorry.
If your hand's okay,
go outside and ask around for a bowl.
That should be enough to dull them, right?
I'm definitely going to cut myself.
Good grief.
Why did my spiritual powers
have to just up and disappear?
My spiritual powers are gone,
and soon my feet will be gone too.
What is she doing here?
How long has she been there?
Did she hear everything?
I need to borrow a gourd bowl.
What?
A gourd bowl.
Right, a gourd bowl.
Yeah, okay.
GARAK SHAMAN
What the heck?
So she really doesn't have
spiritual powers.
AN MENTAL HEALTH CLINIC
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I'll work on the handover,
so find my replacement as soon as you can.
You're really doing this?
How can we work together
after breaking up?
-Hey, Min Su-ji.
-Yeah, what?
Do you even have somewhere to go
if you quit?
I'll figure something out.
That's not what I meant.
Why do I keep saying things like that?
Damn it.
What? Well, look who it is! It's Su-ji!
-Have you been well?
-Of course!
What brings you to Taffy Village?
I just thought I'd stop by.
Can I get a kimchi stew
and a bottle of soju?
Of course.
Feels like yesterday you were in uniform.
Now you're old enough to drink?
Oh, aren't you pretty!
Su-ji, you're old enough
to get married now.
What's with the marriage talk
from the get-go?
Are you happy because you're married?
Didn't you say that night at the motel
near Gujin rotary with Pil-seung's father
was the biggest mistake of your life?
Su-ji, don't you ever get married.
But still,
if everyone's married,
and you're the only one left,
it would get lonely.
I guess you're right.
Come to think of it,
aren't you the same age as Tae-ha?
-That's right.
-Yeah.
Tae-ha brought home a wife he adores
and started a family.
-Su-ji, don't you have anyone?
-Don't you?
No, I don't.
Have a drink. Go on.
WALNUTS
BOOSTS BRAIN HEALTH AND MEMORY
Thank you.
Su-ji, will you be okay?
-I'm totally fine. I swear.
-Goodness, I'm worried.
-I'll get going.
-Careful now.
Will you be okay?
Jang Tae-ha.
You're…
Su-ji. Min Su-ji.
Don't you dare call me Sun-deok again.
Right.
Are you okay?
If I'm not okay,
will you take me home?
Look at that.
I have to get home.
Right, Gi-jun.
You work with Gi-jun, don't you? Hold on.
She grabbed his hand!
Don't.
What?
I'm saying don't call him.
If I were your girlfriend,
could I have been loved too?
Stop right there.
-What is it?
-Eun-sae's here.
Go Eun-sae.
No need to be flustered.
Just do as I say from now on.
Arms by your sides.
Three steps back.
You're dead meat.
Excuse me.
Your fly's open.
I won't assume you're 100% faking
being drunk.
But if you had enough sense
to zip up your damn fly,
you shouldn't be grabbing
a taken man's hand.
Your address.
Jangmi Mansion.
Jangmi Mansion?
Okay.
Hi, Gang-rok.
You told me to think of you
as a little brother at my disposal,
so do me a favor.
There's a drunk lady over here.
Please escort her home.
How impressive.
Impact detected.
The car's nice, isn't it?
The plastic wrap is still on.
Shall we tear it off together later?
Forget the plastic wrap.
I wanted to tear out that girl's hair
but held myself back,
so let's just go quietly.
You know, I only held her up.
So she wouldn't fall.
If you face-plant on asphalt,
you're in big trouble.
You could shatter your cheekbones.
Why are that woman's cheekbones
any of your concern?
Huh?
It's as if you want to save
the entire world.
Is it your dream to be an Avenger?
Don't you know how to draw lines?
You shouldn't have left her an opening.
You let her touch…
Why would you let her touch you?
Only I'm allowed to do that. Only me.
You're smiling?
Is this funny to you?
Do you think
I'm being jealous or something?
I'm talking about basic common sense here.
Okay, it was wrong of me.
I'm sorry.
I'm serious.
See what'll happen
if you ever touch another woman again.
What's that?
Some walnuts.
They look like brains,
so they're brain food.
To help you regain your memory.
Come on, that's ridiculous.
So, what, you drink milk
if you want fair skin
and eat gochujang if you want red lips?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I think
I remember something.
Go Ji-won!
I said I'll make you eat gochujang
if you leave food, didn't I?
Eat it!
Eat! I said eat!
Open!
Open your mouth! Wide! Open!
Thank you.
Feel better?
Yeah.
I guess the treatment I got today worked.
You remembered being at the orphanage?
Yes.
Not all of it,
but bits and pieces, here and there.
After I woke up with my memory gone,
I really didn't want to go
to a government facility for some reason.
Now I know why.
I guess my body remembered.
I told you to smile big
when they come to take pictures.
At the orphanage,
we got group punishments all the time.
Go Ji-won!
In the middle of winter,
we were often kicked out barefoot.
Outside.
Just thinking about
how the cold crept into my feet…
It still gives me the chills.
They abused you?
Being kids without guardians
made us easy targets.
And another thing.
We were dragged off to work.
What?
On weekends, we went to a rural area
about three hours away
to work on a farm.
I remember the trip to the country
being really rough.
We were all crammed in a van
for three hours.
"Oh, I wish I could find
a discarded MP3 player or something."
"Then I could listen to my favorite
god songs to help me get through it."
I think I had innocent thoughts like that.
Those things were a luxury
for kids like me.
And
there were also thugs
who took the orphanage's funds.
When they got angry,
they would beat up
the middle school boys at the orphanage.
I was terrified.
I guess that's why
I hate violence so much.
What do you hate, Tae-ha?
What?
I don't have any memories,
so I don't know much about you.
Tell me everything again, one by one.
First off, your favorite things are
boxing and gochujang stew.
Next, what don't you like?
Rain.
Rain?
On the hardest days of my life,
it always rained, for some reason.
BODEUM HOSPITAL CANCER CENTER
Like the day Grandma collapsed…
and the day I quit boxing.
Just… days like those.
TAEREUNG NATIONAL TRAINING CENTER
In my bleakest moments,
there was nothing
to shield me from the rain.
It felt like
a reminder of just how hopeless
things were.
So I don't like rain.
I heard your story from Mr. Hong.
Don't you regret
the decision you made back then?
I don't.
Because I protected
what I wanted to protect.
Thank you.
For protecting me too.
If it had been anyone else,
I think they would've given up on me
when I lost my memory and my mind.
Now that I have some of my memories back,
I'm even more grateful to you.
I'm glad
that you're my boyfriend.
I'm back!
Right, yeah.
Hello.
-You're… here.
-Why do you have the lights off?
I took the drunk lady home.
I even rode the taxi with her
and saw her get inside safely.
And on my way back, I saw someone
selling flower-shaped buns.
Here.
Would you like some?
Buns at this hour?
I ought to kick you in the buns.
Yeah, eating them will only make you fat.
You're starting to get a belly.
HONG'S BOXING GYM
I got some nice sea bream at the market
and cooked it for you all.
-I forgot water.
-I'll get it.
No, please.
It's just that…
Why would you let her touch you?
Only I'm allowed to do that. Only me.
I was told not to make
any physical contact with other women.
What a load of crap.
Are you out of your mind?
Just leave him be.
He sure learned that well.
Give that here.
Eun-sae, will you be going
to the taffy shop today?
The shop is closed today.
Then shall we go to see the ritual?
-The ritual?
-Yeah.
Maeng-suk is performing
a shamanic ritual today.
I see.
Wait, I'm sorry.
I forgot that I had something to do today.
I was the one who suggested it,
but I'm flaking.
I'll be back after a quick call.
Please go ahead.
Why is he moving around so much
with that injured foot of his?
Just leave him be.
Wow, this soup is really something.
Is it?
That was delicious.
You're leaving already?
We finished eating.
I'll get going.
Okay. Remember to take your meds
and call if anything happens.
See you later.
Are you that happy?
Why are you doing this?
-Follow me quietly.
-Sorry?
But, sir!
My leg…
Seriously, why are you doing this?
Tell me. What are you up to?
Did Baek Sang-gil send you?
No. Why would he send me?
I didn't even see his face when I left--
Keep it down, damn it.
Then who are you reporting to,
and about what?
Where do you go at dawn?
And why do you have two phones?
Explain it all. In detail.
I…
do YouTube live streams.
-What?
-I review overseas soccer games.
The phones.
I have two because I watch soccer on one
while I film myself with the other.
I've been leaving at dawn to stream
because that's when overseas games happen.
I couldn't do it at home,
where you guys were sleeping.
And he goes for it!
Up the field. On the other side!
Oh, Ashley!
This one's for you guys!
Thank you!
Guys, thank…
I cover my face,
and I avoid places that might give away
where we are, so you don't have to worry.
And the calls are with my YouTube agency.
They ask me when I can stream.
The calls were me sharing my schedule.
I quit the gang,
but I still needed to make a living.
And my foot was like this.
There was nothing I could do.
So I asked myself,
"What was it that I truly liked?"
"What did I want to become?"
That's how I started doing this.
If you don't believe me,
check for yourself.
Hello, this is Studio Yes,
a YouTube content agency.
Why is this so scuffed?
When does the cast come off?
I understand why you're so worried.
Because if Chairman Baek…
I mean, if Baek Sang-gil finds out,
neither you nor the prosecutor
will survive.
The stowaway boat plan is getting close.
Is the prosecutor getting better?
Yesterday, she remembered her childhood.
She'll likely regain her memory soon.
I really hope that happens.
If it does, it will be easier
to persuade her to leave the country,
but wouldn't she also find out
that you're not her boyfriend?
That would mean losing
the relationship you have now.
Will you be okay with that?
It doesn't matter what happens to me
as long as Go Eun-sae lives.
-She's getting on the blades.
-She is!
It's so fascinating.
What's taking her so long?
-What's going on?
-She's not getting on.
-Why isn't she getting on them?
-What's she doing?
Hurry up already!
Snake! It's a snake!
-Snake?
-A snake?
A snake! There's a snake!
What the heck?
Isn't it bad luck to see snakes
or animal carcasses during a ritual?
Yeah, they say you shouldn't perform
a shamanic ritual if you see a snake.
They say it won't work.
It's no good if it won't work!
Then I guess we should call it a day.
Hey, lady! Come down!
Okay.
Let's stop.
Where did the snake even come from?
I'm going to stop now!
-She's stopping the ritual?
-She's stopping?
Yes!
I'm going to stop!
What's wrong?
What's going on?
-What's going on?
-What's happening?
What…
I tried everything…
but once the spirit leaves,
it doesn't come back.
I'd been thinking about quitting
for a while,
but I couldn't bring myself to do it.
After losing my husband and child,
I only had my fortune-telling business.
If I lost that too,
my life would be too empty.
What, are we just for show?
You have us, two plump women,
under each of your arms.
Why would your life be empty?
That's why you should have
at least told us.
This must have been gnawing at you
all this time…
You guys are right.
I'd briefly forgotten I had two ladies
who loomed large in my life.
I feel so relieved, like I finally got
a whole load of old poop out of my system.
As for you.
Why did you help me?
Well, I had no other choice.
If I had left you alone,
your feet would've been covered in blood.
I guess you're not a total lost cause.
Well, I realized something
after losing my memory.
I had something,
but it disappeared overnight.
I was flustered
and bitter.
It all felt unfair.
But what I lost wouldn't come back.
My emotions were all over the place
dozens of times a day.
It drove me to the brink of insanity.
Then it occurred to me
that you must have felt the same way.
You two were in the same boat?
I guess.
Life is funny, isn't it?
Just the other day
you were fighting over a broken statue.
Who'd have thought that you two
would now be seeing eye to eye?
Tell me about it.
Let's have a drink,
since we see eye to eye.
Cheers!
Let us join in.
-Cheers!
Oh, great spirit!
Never come looking for me again
Don't you dare curse me
For being a cruel woman…
I love you to death
Why don't you believe me?
Until the day I die
You're the only one for me
Actually, no, even if I die
You'd still be the only one for me
So please open your heart, believe me
And love me
I love you, ladies!
Careful.
You sexy man, you're my man
You handsome man, you're my man
When this world ends
I'll lose myself in a fantasy
Why did you make her drink so much?
-What?
-Hey!
No, we didn't make her drink.
Your wifey did it all by herself.
It was yummy.
Your wifey is approved! Approved by us!
Approved!
Ladies, let's go for a third round!
-Let's go.
-Sounds good!
Then should we go to the club in town
with the roof that opens?
Let's go!
What are you talking about?
Please get home safely.
Let's go!
My sexy man
-Let's get you home.
-I want to go!
-I can drink more.
-No, you'll die if you drink more.
Hey, it's my boyfriend,
Jang Tae-ha.
Go to sleep.
Okay.
But don't go anywhere
until I fall asleep.
Okay.
If she remembers everything,
that would mean losing
the relationship you have now.
Will you be okay with that?
I'm told that multiple guys
have seen Prosecutor Go.
They saw Go Ji-won?
At first, I also thought
it was impossible, but…
-Hey.
-What is it?
Isn't that Prosecutor Go?
Even though they saw her
at different locations,
their descriptions of her outfit
were identical.
Given the circumstances,
I thought I should tell you first.
If it really is Go Ji-won,
does that mean Jang Tae-ha lost her?
That,
or he let her live.
Impossible.
Sir, what's more worrying
is what Gwak Chi-hyeon said.
Prosecutor Go said she had prepared
one more thing besides the watch.
If Prosecutor Go really is alive,
it's suspicious that she's been quiet.
She could be preparing something
with what Gwak Chi-hyeon mentioned.
My stomach's killing me.
How much did I drink last night?
This is my boyfriend.
He studied international relations
at Hanguk University
and is now the Gangju mayor's aide.
Nice to meet you. I'm Gwak Chi-hyeon.
What… is this?
What is this memory?
He's my boyfriend?
Is he an ex-boyfriend?
I've heard a lot about you from the mayor.
I look forward to your support.
No, it's recent.
-Did you say we dated for two years?
-Yeah.
What is this?
Did you get some sleep?
Is your stomach okay?
Yes.
By any chance,
did I…
Yes?
Never mind.
-You remembered that?
-Yes.
But it doesn't make sense.
I've been dating Jang Tae-ha
for two years.
Why would I introduce someone
named Gwak Chi-hyeon as my boyfriend?
So I was wondering,
could this be a memory of a dream
or something I imagined?
I'm not sure.
It's not completely impossible.
But there's no way to be sure.
Wait a minute.
Actually, there might be a way.
-How?
-Didn't you say he studied at Hanguk Uni?
-Yes.
-I went to med school there!
Look behind you.
Hold on, one second.
Let me check with a friend
who was in that department.
DIRECTOR AN GI-JUN
HANGUK UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF MEDICINE
CHAIRMAN BAEK SANG-GIL
How did it go?
They're yet to find CCTV footage
of the person they think is Prosecutor Go.
If that bitch really is alive,
we don't have time to waste like this.
Find her in two days, no matter what.
How did it go?
Unbelievable.
There really was a guy named
Gwak Chi-hyeon in that department.
And… Take a seat.
My friend gave me his number.
So,
do you want to find out
if your memory is real?
SEOUN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Please, can you stop…
Can you please stop tailing me?
I got fired from my job as an aide.
What could I do in this state…
-Hello?
-Is this Mr. Gwak Chi-hyeon?
Yes, it is.
This is Go Ji-won.
Ji-won?
Hey, Ji-won.
Where are you?
Why haven't you been answering my calls?
I'll explain the details
in person.
Sure. Where should we meet?
Where would be good?
In Seoul.
Tonight, in Seoul.
Okay, let's do that. All right.
A clinic in Seoul?
Yeah.
Since some of her memory has returned,
I thought we could give it a boost
by trying
a more sophisticated form of TMS.
My friend runs a clinic,
and they recently bought
an upgraded TMS machine.
Of course we should go.
When can we go?
Tonight.
-Tonight?
-Yeah.
They're fully booked for a while,
so today is the only open slot.
Let's go.
But you have a lesson tonight.
I can just reschedule it.
I just happen to have a seminar
in Seoul today.
I'm going to Seoul,
so I can take Ms. Go with me.
-No need to go out of your way.
-It's fine.
One second.
Why is she calling me?
KIM SONG-WOL
Yes?
Grandma!
-Ma'am?
-What's wrong?
Grandma, what's wrong? What is it?
What?
DEPARTMENT OF NUCLEAR MEDICINE
PET-CT SCAN ROOM
She has a tumor.
If it's malignant,
can she get surgery like last time?
Well, her body is much weaker
than it was 14 years ago,
so it would be more complicated.
Let's wait for the test results first.
Okay.
I think I should stay with Grandma today.
You should go to Seoul with Gi-jun.
No, I'll go next time.
You should go. Today's your only chance.
Your treatment
is as important to me as Grandma.
Grandma would want that too.
-Thanks.
-It's nothing.
These are your meds. Take them on time.
I'll be back.
Wait. Can you wait just a little?
Mr. Hong's coming.
What?
Why is he coming?
I asked him to go with you.
You have your seminar.
Someone should take care of Eun-sae.
There's no need.
I don't want to go with a stranger, okay?
-We'll be fine.
-Yes.
I don't want Mr. Hong
rescheduling his lessons for me.
-Still…
-I won't leave her alone.
Don't worry. See you when we get back.
Hey, Gi-jun.
Yes, Doctor?
Has my grandma woken up?
This is Go Ji-won.
Ji-won?
Hey, Ji-won.
Where are you?
Why haven't you been answering my calls?
I'll explain the details
in person.
Let's say
this man called Gwak Chi-hyeon
really is your boyfriend.
What then?
If that's the case,
it would be one of two things.
Either Jang Tae-ha's fake,
or I was two-timing.
Whatever the case,
I think I'll be really sad.
Grandma.
Yeah?
What?
Are you okay?
Am I… sick?
We don't know yet.
We have to wait for the test results.
Don't you worry.
I won't die that easily.
After everything you did to save my life,
how could I possibly…
I'm going to hold on tight and protect it.
You promise?
Yes, of course.
Don't you know how strong I am?
No matter how hard the disease
tries to get me,
it won't stand a chance against me.
No way.
My precious baby.
My absolute blessing.
I'm going to be fine.
You should go home and sleep comfortably.
Okay?
Go on home.
Go on.
I'm going to get some sleep.
Go on home.
BODEUM HOSPITAL CANCER CENTER
Go Eun-sae.
You…
What happened to you?
What about the treatment?
Time for my meds.
In the middle of winter,
we were often kicked out barefoot.
Just thinking about
how the cold crept into my feet…
It still gives me the chills.
Turns out MP3 players are still around.
Listen to this if you get carsick.
"Oh, I wish I could find
a discarded MP3 player or something."
"Then I could listen to my favorite
god songs to help me get through it."
Those things were a luxury
for kids like me.
01. GOD - ONE CANDLE
02. GOD - LOVE YOU AND…
Jang Tae-ha, you…
What's wrong? Did you remember something?
What the…
Right, rain's forecast nationwide tonight.
Doctor,
let's just go back.
What?
I need to go back.
What are you talking about?
You're just going back
without even checking the facts?
This can't be fake.
Jang Tae-ha is real.
So let's just go back.
I want to go to Tae-ha right now.
I asked about your treatment.
Did you get it already?
If I said that I was more worried about
you getting caught in the rain
than recovering my memory…
would you believe me?
Even if I can't do much else for you,
on hard days like tonight,
I thought I could at least shield you
from the rain.
I really wanted to do that for you.
In my bleakest moments,
there was nothing
to shield me from the rain.
It felt like a reminder
of just how hopeless things were.
So I don't like rain.
Let's weather it together from now on.
I'll be with you.
OUR STICKY LOVE
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi